# **Christopher Ganesh McMahon**

Website | GitHub | LinkedIn

469 396 1702 | 505 E Exchange Pkwy 10301 Allen, TX 75002 | mctopherganesh@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Self taught programmer specializing in rapid prototyping and tooling with Python and extensive direct customer service and sales background. Highly motivated to deliver results and eliminate waste in an environment with complex challenges in data engineering or science.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Wisconsin Stevens Point, Stevens Point, WI

- Bachelors of Science American Studies
- Date Graduated:December 2014
- Relevant coursework: emphasis in Web Development and Economics

Data Analyst Pre-Apprentice, Digital Creative Institute, San Antonio, TX

Oct 2019-Present

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Quality Assurance Assistant, Freelance (Remote) GTGUK Services LTD., UK

Apr 2018-Apr 2020

- Evaluate all new website functionality, products, purchasing flows, and tracking of all marketing email funnels
- Investigate and identify bugs, typos, deformities, and all other customer interaction and process errors
- Design communication standards in QA department to enhance department productivity
- Developed automated browser testing framework with Python Selenium
- Addressed and solved questions and concerns from customers while working in customer service

#### Sale Associate, The UPS Store, Winter Park, FL

Oct 2016-Nov 2017

- Interacted professionally and built rapport to maintain or create new customer relationships
- Collected and collated accurate incoming and outgoing package data
- Arranged multi-piece freight shipments both domestically and internationally

## Outbound Sales Agent, Hilton Grand Vacations, Orlando, FL

Apr 2016-Sept 2016

- Generated rapport with new customers
- Achieved sales of vacation packages to previous Hilton guests and Hilton Honors Members
- Adapted guickly and creatively to resolve customer problems or concerns

## Keystone Property Management: Night Operations Group, Keystone Resort, Keystone, CO

Dec 2014-Mar 2016

- Serviced the nightly needs of over 750 properties, their guests/owners, and the resort at large
- Managed work orders and organized logistics for guest requests

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Recess and Afterschool Program Volunteer, St. Stainslaus Grade School, Stevens Point, WI Front-Desk Reception, Elevate Coworking Space, Frisco, CO

Nov 2010-Feb 2011 May 2015-Mar 2016

## **AWARDS & COMPETITIONS**

Walmart Pandas Hackathon, Walmart Technology, Dallas, TX

Aug 16-Aug 18

### **SKILLS**

**Technical:** Coding (Advanced: Python | Intermediate: SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, R), Microsoft Suite (Intermediate: Excel, Powerpoint, Word), OS (Advanced: Linux, OSX, Windows)